[
	{
    id: "1",
    image: "",
    question: "Bu anime karakteri hangi animeden?",
    optionOne: "Fullmetal Alchemist",
    optionTwo: "Cowboy Bebop",
    optionTree: "Space Dandy",
    optionFour: "Simoun",
    correctAnswer: "2"
	},
	{
    id: "2",
    image: "",
    question: "Bu anime karakteri hangi animeden?",
    optionOne: "Eden of the East",
    optionTwo: "Shinging Tears X Wind",
    optionTree: "When the Cry",
    optionFour: "Diabolik Lovers",
    correctAnswer: "3"
	},
	{
    id: "3",
    image: "",
    question: "Bu anime karakteri hangi animeden?",
    optionOne: "Charlotte",
    optionTwo: "Guilty Cown",
    optionTree: "Yuki Yuna is Hero",
    optionFour: "Angel Beats",
    correctAnswer: "4"
	},
	{
    id: "4",
    image: "",
    question: "Bu anime karakteri hangi animeden?",
    optionOne: "Monster",
    optionTwo: "Elfen Lied",
    optionTree: "Black Jack",
    optionFour: "Fullmetal Alchemist",
    correctAnswer: "1"
	},
	{
    id: "5",
    image: "",
    question: "Bu anime karakteri hangi animeden?",
    optionOne: "Soul Eater",
    optionTwo: "Blue Exorcicst",
    optionTree: "Elfen Lied",
    optionFour: "Brynhildr in the Darkness",
    correctAnswer: "3"
	},
	{
    id: "6",
    image: "",
    question: "Bu anime karakteri hangi animeden?",
    optionOne: "Occult Academy",
    optionTwo: "Rosario Vampire",
    optionTree: "Maria Holic",
    optionFour: "Sword Art Online",
    correctAnswer: "2"
	},
	{
    id: "7",
    image: "",
    question: "Bu anime karakteri hangi animeden?",
    optionOne: "Noragami",
    optionTwo: "Sailor Moon",
    optionTree: "Dragon Ball",
    optionFour: "Fairy Tail",
    correctAnswer: "4"
	},
  {
    id: "8",
    image: "",
    question: "Bu anime karakteri hangi animeden?",
    optionOne: "My Hero Academia",
    optionTwo: "Hunter X Hunter",
    optionTree: "Bleach",
    optionFour: "High School DxD",
    correctAnswer: "2"
	},
   {
    id: "9",
    image: "",
    question: "Bu anime karakteri hangi animeden?",
    optionOne: "Date a Live",
    optionTwo: "Re:Zero - Starting Life in Other World",
    optionTree: "	No Game No Life",
    optionFour: "Swort Art Online",
    correctAnswer: "3"
	},
   {
    id: "10",
    image: "",
    question: "Bu anime karakteri hangi animeden?",
    optionOne: "Black Lagon",
    optionTwo: "Dragon Ball",
    optionTree: "Tokyo ghoul",
    optionFour: "Naruto",
    correctAnswer: "4"
	}
]
